HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
We are going to call most especially those people from other countries
that have broken homes.
The reason we listen to them is to strengthen your desire for God,
to prepare you for the challenges ahead, to keep you for a new level,
for you to know that with God all things are possible.
So, when you listen to them, what should be going through your mind is
‘I need to forgive; I need to be forgiven.’
Tell your neighbour.
Again.
‘I need to forgive; I need to be forgiven.’
My name is Beatrice Nbone, I am from Cameroon.
The problem that brought me here is that my family accused me of being a witch.
Five years ago, when my big sister died, they went to a witch doctor.
When they came back, they said that I was the one that killed her.
My brother died; they said that I killed him.
My sister’s daughter died; they said that I was the one that killed her.
This very year, an eleven months old baby died;
they said that I was the one who killed him.
When it was time for the baby’s burial, they said that they must kill me
because if they left me, I would still kill more people.
So, they caught me, put me in a room and locked the door
and sent some boys to go and get petrol to burn me.
So, suddenly a ‘good Samaritan’ went to call my friend.
She passed through the back door with some other boys.
She took me through the back door and ran with me to her house.
She kept me in her house, we looked for money and she brought me here.
I beg the man of God to tell the whole of Cameroon if I am a witch or not.
He should help me because I’ve cried too much.
I beg the man of God to help me.
The trouble is too much.
Man of God, help me.
I cry every day. I don’t have peace; help me.
How do you know that they wanted to take petrol and burn you?
I was listening as they were talking about it.
A ‘good Samaritan’ called my friend who came with some boys
and they passed through a back door and rescued me.
I’m Likambi Anita from Cameroon.
I am here on behalf of my friend.
Five years ago, she was accused by the family of being a witch.
When she lost her senior sister, they went to a witch doctor
and the witch doctor told them that she was the cause of the death of her sister.
After that death, the senior brother died.
They said that it was her again.
After that, her sister’s daughter died and they said it was her.
This year, a small baby of eleven months died.
This one was the worst.
They decided that it was too much.
They even said she had a blanket she was using in the witchcraft world.
I shouldn't be close to her because she would use that blanket to cover my progress.
So that day that they wanted to bury that small boy,
they locked her inside a room, sent boys to go and buy petrol
and said that they would burn her.
So, I came and took her away to my place.
When she was crying, I told her not to cry, that the answer is The SCOAN.
Everybody back home now is watching to hear the man of God say something about this situation.
If the man of God doesn’t say anything, we cannot go back because they will kill her.
It is an idol that is fighting the villagers; not this woman.
This woman is not a witch.
Man of God, thank you.
Thank you, man of God.
She is not a witch.
It is the idol that their forefathers worshipped that is fighting.
But by the time she goes back home with the Anointing Water, the idol will run away.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
The idol uses the appearance of this woman to do all this.
She is not the one.
She is a human being just like anyone.
She is not a witch.
She is totally innocent.
I want to pray for everyone in the village that God should forgive them.
I know they are watching this program and they have honour and respect to God.
The Holy Spirit is a supreme agent.
No matter what they might have believed in, they know there is power above.
I want to thank the sister; the Spirit of God really used you to do the job; very clean job.
Give the Anointing Water.
In the name of Jesus.
Watch your screen.
See what is happening.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
In the name of Jesus.
When you take it, you are set aside for the Lord's attention.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
When you are set aside for the Lord's attention, what happens next -
you will find yourself under the influence of the Holy Ghost.
This is the position of the Holy Spirit.
I am Maria Kambasha, I come from Zimbabwe.
I am one of the people who has accused my father’s brother,
my uncle, that he is a wizard.
After he had a shrine in his home, there were so many deaths in the family.
Children died, his wife died, his brothers died and my father died.
So, I went to a witch doctor, and he bathed us -
me and my family and the other family.
We were given ropes to tie around our waist for protection.
I have it here.
I’ve got the rope under here.
In 1999, where I was married, there was a wicked brother to my husband.
He also has a shrine where we believed he drinks people’s blood.
So, there are deaths often – the 16th of May every year, a man dies.
Since my husband died in 1999 up until now, we have deaths every 16th of May.
So, I came here to The SCOAN
to seek for deliverance of my family.
I fear death; death is all over.
I fear for my children.
I need deliverance so I came here.
On Monday when the man of God touched us,
that night, this wicked man came to my dream and asked me, “Why have you gone to T.B. Joshua?”
I said, “I am afraid.”
He said, “I did not kill your children.”
Then I said, “You killed my husband.”
He said, “After all, that was my brother.”
Man of God, I am here for deliverance.
She needs to go back to the family.
This is why God has given the Anointing Water.
Any newcomer, a person coming here for the first time - come, sir.
You just take deliverance out of it and go and minister it.
What you are going to say,
I need to forgive; I need to be forgiven.
Lord, have mercy on me.
Let your mercy and favour speak for me today, in Jesus' name. Amen.
After that you spray it...
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
I minister to you in the name of Jesus, the blood of Jesus.
The Anointing Water for healing and deliverance.
See what is happening.
Down she goes.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
Maria from Zimbabwe was delivered after receiving the Anointing Water.
My name is Philip Mweene from Zambia.
I am 62 years old.
I had six daughters and two boys.
I have accused my elder sister of killing my three daughters.
What happened was that when they were pregnant and about to give birth,
the whole body would swell up from head to toe.
The first one died in 1999.
As Christians we depended on God and we surrendered the whole issue to God.
The second one died in 2005 - this one shocked the entire family.
The entire family forced us to go and look for a witch doctor.
We went together with the family and the witch doctor pointed out that
it is my elder sister who was responsible for all these deaths.
But again in 2008, a third one died in the same way.
The fourth one, Mary – I’ve got her picture.
She is pregnant and she is suffering in the same way like the others who have died.
When we saw this, it annoyed me and the entire family.
So we organised ourselves and said, “Let us go to a very powerful witch doctor.”
I sold about eight herds of cattle and the money came to $960.
While we were contemplating this, well wishers, friends
and other relatives came to me and said, “Mr Philip,
you have gone to many witch doctors. This time, why don’t you change this money you have,
because it can take you to Nigeria to see Prophet T.B. Joshua for this case.
Then we started to organise the journey.
They said, “If you go there, you will be delivered,
the entire family will be delivered and even the one responsible for the deaths will be delivered.
That is how I myself am here.
I ask the man of God to help me, to help the family
because in the family, there is a curse – always dreaming of funerals, of death and so forth.
The woman they call a witch is not a witch.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
I can't understand the way you people catch witches and wizards.
You mean that darkness can catch darkness?
Give the Anointing Water - let her spray it by herself.
As instructed, she removes the Anointing Water from its box and ministers it to the man.
In Jesus' name...
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
It worked so powerfully; you need to know what you carry.
OK, spray it into your mouth.
She has lost control of herself.
Down she goes.
It is something that fights darkness.
If there is any atom of darkness in your body, it will release you.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
Collect it from her and give it to baba.
Apply it to yourself.
That is the man from Zambia.
Down he goes.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
If there is anything satan might have used to connect them to himself, they have been disconnected.
Now delivered, they are free, in Jesus Christ's name.
Thank You, Jesus.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us – Matthew 1:23)
If God is with us, who can be against us?
Thank You, Jesus.
Viewers all over the world, thank you for being part of this broadcast.
We pray the Lord will give you a hearing heart.
We shall quickly look at the Word Jesus has for us.
The title: “Broken Home And Reconciliation”
Tell your neighbour.
Broken Home And Reconciliation
Viewers all over the world, open with me the Book of Isaiah 11.
“There shall come forth a Rod from the stem of Jesse,
and a Branch shall grow out of his roots."
Verse 2: “The Spirit of the Lord shall rest upon Him,
the Spirit of wisdom and understanding,
the Spirit of counsel and might,
the Spirit of knowledge and of the fear of the Lord."
Verse 3: “His delight is in the fear of the Lord…”
That is his joy is in the fear of the Lord.
When you now look at verse 6:
“The wolf also shall dwell with the lamb…”
These are the two that one would not expect.
For the wolf to dwell with the lamb – this means there is reconciliation.
Without the Gospel of grace, the wolf cannot dwell with the lamb.
There are things that just don’t belong together.
Good example of it is the wolf and the lamb.
There are things that just don’t belong together:
light and darkness.
the lion and the deer.
Broken Home And Reconciliation
Let someone say.
You see these two things: light and darkness, wolf and lamb, lion and deer;
they are things that just don't belong together.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
A son will never call his father’s murderer, “Dear friend”.
There are things that just don’t belong together.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
The Gospel of God’s grace challenges and changes everything.
To His power nothing is impossible.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
When you take your time to read the Book of Mark 11 from verse 25 - hear forgiveness.
Jesus clearly linked faith to forgiveness.
The reason forgiveness is so important is that
a relationship does not involve two perfect people.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
There is no such thing as a perfect person.
Tell your neighbour.
Those perfect people don’t exist on this earth.
Those perfect people don’t exist on this planet.
Tell your neighbour once again.
Those perfect people don’t exist on this earth.
There is no such thing as a perfect person.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
Let someone say, "Broken Home And Reconciliation".
People make mistakes, even if you are a Christian, even if you are a pastor.
Our response to a person who makes mistakes can also be a mistake.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
Tell your neighbour.
Our response to a person who makes mistakes can also be a mistake, if care is not taken.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
Let someone say, "Broken Home And Reconciliation".
Our concern must be twofold: not only what we do that is in error but also how we respond.
Tell your neighbour,
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
Our concern must be twofold: not only what we do that is in error but also how we respond
because you need to forgive and you need to be forgiven.
Tell your neighbour,
You need to forgive and you need to be forgiven.
Our response to a person who makes mistakes can also be a mistake.
Our concern must be twofold: not only what we do that is in error
but also how we respond -
because you need to forgive; you need to be forgiven.
Tell your neighbour,
I need to forgive; I need to be forgiven.
Take to the Book of Galatians 6,
“Brethren, if a man is overtaken in any trespass,
you who are spiritual restore such…
considering yourself lest you also be tempted.”
If you are spiritual, when someone falls, don’t rejoice - restore.
Tell your neighbour,
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
Let's go to the Book of 1 Peter 4:8.
“And above all things have fervent love for one another…”
Wow.
Love does not discuss sin.
Tell your neighbour.
You know the meaning of that?
- Come; do you know - he is a drunkard, I saw him, he doesn't sleep at home.
- Wow.
- He is a drunkard.
Because I have no love, he has no love; that is why he is listening.
If he had love, he would know that love does not discuss sin.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
If your faith is lifted up, let me see your hand.
Love does not draw attention to sin.
It is far from many of us here.
You say you love but you don't practise love.
By your action, by your deed, your character - no...
Love does not discuss sin because you need to forgive and you need to be forgiven.
As I have said, our response to error, mistake, trouble can also be a mistake.
When I stand with this man saying, "He is a drunkard", I too am a drunkard - I made a mistake.
God has written us into an unprecedented and revolutionary story of reconciliation
in which hostilities are destroyed and enemies become friends.
Parents play with their children and put their arms around them.
The generation of vipers shall become a seed of saints.
You unbelieving generation, how long shall I stay with you?
How long shall I put up with you?
Now, bring the boy!
I mean generation without faith, without hope.
This generation of vipers shall become a seed of saints.
Look at the case of Paul.
When Paul who had persecuted the saints joined himself to them,
the wolf dwelt with the lamb.
Man is a wolf to man.
Man is a lion to man.
Man is a snake to man.
When Paul who had persecuted the saints joined himself to them,
the wolf dwelt with the lamb.
Man is a wolf to man.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
Let someone say,
Man is a snake to man.
Man is a lion to man.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
The Gospel of God’s grace challenges and changes everything.
Tell your neighbour,
The right knowledge of God settles peace.
The Word of God is preached everywhere, but there are right ones.
This is why I say, the right knowledge of God settles peace.
There are messages everywhere - minus miracles in the ministry become philosophers.
You yourself are a miracle.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
There are many miracles; I can just tell you one.
You were once a tiny embryo; look at what you have become today.
A tiny embryo.
Is that not miracle?
I am serving the Lord of miracles
I know yes I know
For you to sleep and wake up is a miracle.
The answer to your prayer is a miracle.
If you know there is no answer to your prayer, you stop praying.
Because you know there is an answer to your prayer, that answer is a miracle.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
Thank you. I will now come to the end of this message.
The reason forgiveness is so important is that
relationship does not involve two perfect people.
There is no such thing as a perfect person.
Those perfect people don’t exist on this earth.
As a Christian, you are living by grace.
This is what we mean by the Gospel of God's grace challenges and changes everything -
those things that just don’t belong together -
where today the lion and the deer will eat straw side by side.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
The wolf and the lamb will lie down together.
The lion and the calf will eat straw side by side.
This is the Gospel of God’s grace – challenges and changes everything.
To His power nothing is impossible.
Because of who You are
I give You glory
I give You praise
Because of who You are
I will lift my voice and say
Lord I worship You
Because of who You are
I will worship You
Thank you, you may be seated.
Our response to a person who makes mistakes can also be a mistake.
Because your response is also a sin.
Because I told you that love does not discuss sin.
Love does not draw attention to sin.
Oh, I love Jesus.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
As from today, our concern must be twofold:
not only what we do that is in error but also how we respond.
Say to yourself, "I need to forgive. I need to be forgiven. Thank You, Jesus."
Because the same God that says, "Thou shall not lie", also says, "Thou shall not kill".
If you have lied, you are also a killer.
The right knowledge of God settles peace.
Tell your neighbour.
When you receive the right knowledge of God, you yourself will know that
victims and perpetrators stand in helpless need of His divine forgiveness.
Tell your neighbour.
Whether you are a victim or perpetrator, you stand in helpless need of His divine forgiveness.
Who needs forgiveness?!
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
The right knowledge of God settles peace.
When you hear this, you will not put yourself in the position of a judge.
I need to forgive; I need to be forgiven.
Tell your neighbour.
Because there is no such thing as a perfect person.
Those perfect people don't exist on this earth.
Tell your neighbour,
The right knowledge of God settles peace.
You have peace when you hear the knowledge of God.
You will now know that, "OK, I'm still a friend of God".
You may be poor and yet be a candidate of Heaven.
You may be sick in body and yet be a friend of Jesus.
The way and manner God executes His plan...
God used a thorn to humble Paul.
Who knows what God might have used to humble you, to keep you alive;
it could be disappointment, setback, sickness - God can use any foolish thing.
Tell your neighbour,
The right knowledge of God settles peace.
When you receive this right knowledge, you will not concentrate on your situation;
the poor will not concentrate on his poverty, while the rich will not concentrate on his wealth.
Tell your neighbour,
Because a man may be rich and yet be a friend of God,
a man may be poor and yet be a friend of God.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
Tell your neighbour,
The right knowledge of God settles peace.
Thank you.
HEARTBREAKING: The 'WITCH' They Tried To BURN ALIVE!!!
TT ROBERT BEGIER 06/02/2019
RV: Mel Flowers 24/02/2019